ILGWU. Chicago Joint Board records 5780/044
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Contributions, 1954-1971 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  Finance Committee reports.
- Defant, Geraldine Gordon, Union Representative, 1947-1956 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  Corres. re Union activities.
- Diane Co., Inc., 1952-1954 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Dubinsky, David, 1933-1937 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  1933-Aug, 1937. Corres. bet. Midwest Region & President's Office on all facets of Union activities.
- Dubinsky, David, 1937-1940 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  Sept, 1937-40.
- Dubinsky, David, 1941-1946 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Dubinsky, David, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Dubinsky, David, 1951-1953 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Dubinsky, David, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Dubinsky, David, 1956-1960 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Dubinsky, David, 1960-1963 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Essays for Summer School, Madison, Wisc., 1944 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Federation of Union Representatives, 1961-1963 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Financial Reports, Jt. Bd. and Locals, 1947-1949 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Friedlander, Walter, 1943-1944 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board, 1951-1958 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  Reports submitted from Chicago proper & Midwest Dept.
- General Executive Board., 1959-1964 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Goldstein, Morris A., 1944-1947 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  (Secretary-Treasurer of Joint Board)
- Grievance Committee, 1923-1924 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- H.A. Satin and Co., Inc., 1943-1945 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  1951. Incl. case before the NLRB.
- H.A. Satin and Co., Inc., 1941-1945 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  1951. Cont'd.
- Hege, Robert, Indiana Representative, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  Reports on Union activities.
- Impartial Tribunal, Chicago Dress Industry, 1935-1937 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  Cases and decisions.
- Impartial Tribunal, 1943-1944 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  Barrett Hodes (chairman).
- Impartial Tribunal, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Impartial Tribunal, 1946-1948 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Impartial Tribunal, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- ILGWU, Auditing Dept., 1937-1964 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  I.c.w. Siemon L. Hamburger.
- ILGWU, Auditing Dept., 1953-1964 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- ILGWU, Campaign Committee, 1944-1952 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- ILGWU, Education Dept., 1936-1941 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  Corres. w. Mark Starr, forms, printed material.
- ILGWU, Education Dept., 1942-1949 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  Incl. corres., programs & printed material on ILGWU Institute at Madison University School for Workers.
- ILGWU, Education Dept., 1950-1951 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- ILGWU, Education Dept., 1952-1955 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- ILGWU, Education Dept., 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- ILGWU. Justice, 1954-1955 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  1954-June 1955. M. Bialis reports to Justice on Midwest Area.
- ILGWU. Justice, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  July 1955-56.
- ILGWU. Justice, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- ILGWU, Justice, 1960-1963 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- ILGWU. Justice, 1966-1970 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- ILGWU, Legal Dept., 1947-1954 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- ILGWU, Management-Engineering Dept., 1944-1947 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  Reports on firms & corres. w. William Gomberg.
- ILGWU, Management-Engineering Dept., 1948-1955 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- ILGWU, Political Dept., 1949-1954 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- ILGWU, Political Dept., 1955-1961 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- ILGWU, Research Dept., 1939-1941 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  Corres., reports re firms & negotiations.
- ILGWU, Research Dept., 1942-1955 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- ILGWU, Training Institute, 1950-1954 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  I.c.w. Arthur A. Elder.
- ILGWU, Training Institute, 1955-1960 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  I.c.w. Jack Sessions.
- ILGWU, Frederick F. Umhey, 1934-1947 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- ILGWU, Frederick F. Umhey, 1951-1955 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- ILGWU, Union Label Dept., 1959-1967 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- ILGWU, Welfare and Health Benefits Dept., 1951-1954 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Jewish Appeal, Combined, Chicago, 1941-1951 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1946-1955 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1956-1964 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Kirshbaum-Helbraun, Inc., 1938-1945 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Labor's Non-Partisan League, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Lieberman, Elias, 1938-1947 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Locals, Chicago Misc., 1937-1956 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Local 59, 1934 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  Incl. minutes.
- Local 74, Dress Patternmakers of Chicago, 1936-1937 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Local 76, Chicago, 1930-1945 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  Local 76 & 261
- Local 76, 1938-1940 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  Minutes & reports.
- Local 76, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Local 76, 1944-1945 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Local 100, Chicago, 1941-1957 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  Minutes.
- Local 208, Chicago, 1935-1940 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Local 212, Chicago, 1940-1944 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  Incl. materials of the Wage and Hour Div., U.S. Dept. of Labor on the Embroidery Industry.
- Local 212, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  Report on the Embroidery Industry.
- Local 212, 1935-1936 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Local 212, 1938-1941 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Local 261, Chicago, 1938-1941 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Local 261, 1944-1945 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Locals 314 and 381, Chicago, 1942-1959 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Louis Sopkin Co., 1937 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Madison University School for Workers, 1955-1971 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  (ILGWU Region Institute)
- Manuscript. The Kraus Dress Shop by Edna Thomas (pseudonym): n.d. Chapters 1-3. (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Manuscript, The Kraus Dress Shop. Chapters 4-6. (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Manuscript, The Kraus Dress Shop. Chapters 7-10. (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Mayor's Commission on Human Rights, 1949-1950 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Midwest Dept., 1944-1955 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  Office matters; incl. reports from Lou Montenegro & Norbert Ciesil.
- Midwest Dept., 1956-1962 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Midwest ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1954-1958 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Midwest ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Minutes, Arbitration Board on Working Conditions in the Chicago Cloak, Suit and Skirt Industry, 1915 (Box 27)
  Sept, 1915. 2 vols. Julian W. Mack (chairman).
- Minutes, Chicago Joint Board, 1914-1915 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  Aug, 1914-Feb, 1915. 1 vol.
- Minutes, Chicago Jt. Bd., 1934 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  Mar. -April 1934.
- Minutes, Chicago Jt. Bd., 1946-1947 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Minutes, Chicago Jt. Bd., 1948-1949 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Minutes, Chicago Jt. Bd., 1950-1951 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Minutes, Chicago Jt. Bd., 1952-1953 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Minutes, Chicago Jt. Bd., 1954-1955 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Minutes, Chicago Jt. Bd., 1956-1958 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Minutes, Chicago Jt. Bd., 1959-1961 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Minutes, Chicago Jt. Bd., 1962-1965 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Minutes, Chicago Jt. Bd., 1966-1969 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Minutes, Chicago Jt. Bd., 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Minutes, Chicago Jt. Bd., 1972-1974 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Minutes, Chicago Jt. Bd., 1975 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Minutes, Cloak and Suit Makers Retirement Fund, 1950-1962 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  Incl. financial statements.
- Minutes, Coat and Suit Union Health Fund, 1946-1968 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  Incl. agreements and financial statements.
- Minutes and Agreements pox Valley Retirement Fund, 1952-1963 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Minutes, Chicago Health Center, 1951-1954 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  Incl. agreements & financial statements.
- Minutes, Chicago Health Center, 1955-1959 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Minutes, Joint Board Dress Workers Health Fund, 1947-1968 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Minutes, Joint Board Dress Workers Retirement Fund, 1950-1962 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Minutes, Joint Board Dress Workers Welfare Fund, 1950-1961 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Minutes, Midwestern ILGWU Health Fund, 1953-1972 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Minutes, Midwest ILGWU Retirement Fund, 1954-1956 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Minutes, Midwest ILGWU Retirement Fund, 1957-1965 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Minutes, Out-of-Town Cloak Health Fund, 1946-1968 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  Incl. agreements.
- Minutes, 1953-1960 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  Incl. agreements bet. Union affiliates & associations.
- Minutes, United-Union Dressmakers Health and Welfare Funds, 1948-1957 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1932-1934 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Misc. Corres., 1935-1936 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Misc. Corres., 1937-1939 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Misc. Corres., 1940 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Misc. Corres., 1941 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  Jan-Sept, 1941.
- Misc. Corres., 1941-1943 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  Oct, 1941-43.
- Misc. Corres., 1944 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Misc. Corres., 1945 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  Jan. -Sept, 1945.
- Misc. Corres., 1945-1946 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  Oct, 1945-46.
- Misc. Corres., 1947-1949 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  1947-Apr, 1949.
- Misc. Corres., 1949-1951 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  May 1949-June 1951.
- Misc. Corres., 1951-1954 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  July 1951-54.
- Misc. Corres., 1955-1971 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- The Moordale Corporation, 1953-1963 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, 1944-1958 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- National Labor Relations Board, 1937-1941 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  1948. Corres., printed material on elections & cases before NLRB.
- National War Labor Board, 1942-1944 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- The Needle, 1956-1958 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  Published by misc. Union locals, Chicago.
- Negotiations, 1943-1945 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- New York Handkerchief Mfg. Co., 1937-1941 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  Incl. corres., elections, printed material & case before the NLRB.
- N.Y. Handkerchief Mfg. Co., 1937-1941 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  Cont'd.
- N.Y. Hankerchief Mfg. Co., 1937-1941 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- N.Y. Handkerchief Mfg. Co., 1937-1941 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- New York Joint Boards and Miscellaneous Locals, 1936-1954 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- New York Miscellaneous Locals, 1955-1961 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- North-West Ladies' Mfrs. Association, 1924-1927 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Pesotta, Rose, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Phil Maid Lingerie, Inc., 1969 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Pledge for New Members of the Union. n.d. (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Plotkin, Abraham, 1940-1945 (Box 33, Folder 11a-11b)
  Personal.
- Political-Education Dept.: Midwest Region, 1959-1960 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  Philip B. Oliver reports.
- Politics, Local and National, 1940-1953 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Politics, 1956-1963 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Politics, 1963-1969 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Publications, 1935-1936 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  Sept, 1935-Aug, 1936. The Emancipator, Milwaukee. Wisc.
- Publications, 1936-1943 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  Sept, 1936-Sept, 1943. The Emancipator, Milwaukee, Wisc.
- Publications, 1942-1943 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  Good News.
- Publications, 1930-1939 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  Our Justice & Our Aim.
- Publications, 1935-1949 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  Our Voice.
- Publications and Printed Material, 1920 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  Miscellaneous.
- Publications and Printed Material, 1930-1940 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Rhea Garment Mfg. Co., Milwaukee, Wise., 1946 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Rivera, Diego, 1941-1944 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Roosevelt University, 1948-1971 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Rufer, Harry, 1940-1945 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- S and Z Manufacturing Co., 1950-1953 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Schwartz, Harold, 1939-1944 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  Corres. w. Morris Bialis & Abraham Plotkin on negotiations & legal natters.
- Schwartz, Harold, 1945-1958 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  Incl. corres. re Union activities.
- Schwartz, Harold, 1959-1960 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Schwartz, Harold, 1961-1966 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Smoler Bros., Inc., 1939-1953 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Soldiers File, 1942-1945 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  Corres. w. Union members in the armed forces.
- Southeastern Region, 1945-1955 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  I.c.w. John S. Martin re agreement at Cullman, Ala. (Holeproof Hosiery Co. ).
- Speeches and Outlines, 1941-1944 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  Morris Bialis & other Union officers.
- Speeches and Outlines, 1945-1957 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Statistics on Earnings (Wages) in the Garment Industry, 1937-1939 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Stulberg, Louis, 1956-1961 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  Corres. bet. Morris Bialis & Louis Stulberg on Union activities.
- Stulberg, Louis, 1962-1966 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Stulberg, Louis, 1967-1969 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Stulberg, Louis, 1970-1972 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Stulberg, Louis, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Style Piracy Cases, 1938-1941 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Treasury Dept., 1940-1958 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  Bond drives.
- Twenty-fifth Anniversary Celebration, Chicago Joint Board, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Universal Christian Council, 1940 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- With These Hands, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  Showing.
- Photographs. (Box 37, Folder 8)